This only happens to former idols.
こんなさ、アイドルの元だけ
I don't touch my head, it's normal.
頭触れないよ、普通
Fufufu, fufufu, I'm pretending.
フ フフ、フフフ、フリフリしてる
I won't force you to do that today.
今日はそんなの無理やりやらないからね
If you don't like it, then you don't like it.
嫌だったら、さ、嫌だって
But you like edges, right?
でもエッジ好きでしょ?
I thought.
思った
You really like it, right?
本当は好きでしょ?
If you go out for a while.
ちょっと出ると
Pe
ペ
La is really good.
ラ とかすごいうまいやで
No, how many times was that?
いや、何回でしたかね
I felt nourished today.
今日は栄養されたんだよ
Yes, it's all sesame.
うん、ごましきりだね
I am quite aware of beauty.
結構美容には気づいてしてる
I have to work hard as an actress.
なんか女優がんばらなきゃいけないんだよ
That's amazing, Ju.
すごいね、ジュウ
It's delicious.
うまいね
After all, hey, I'm learning not to kiss.
やっぱ、 ねっ、さ、 キスしないとか勉強するの
hey.
ね
Pussy, are you okay?
マ ンコさん、大丈夫?
Ah, it's okay.
あー、大丈夫
Congratulations!
おめでたしちゃった
Congratulations?
おめでたしちゃった?
Because it felt so good.
気持ちよすぎたから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Fufufu, are you crying?
フ フフ、泣いてる?
I'm not crying.
泣いてない
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'm not crying.
泣いてないです
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Eh, can I continue?
え、続けちゃっていい?
Well, if you don't like it, then today...
いや、嫌だったらそんな、 今日は、
I won't force you to do it.
無理やりやらないから
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょう?
Good.
よいしょ
Do you want to leave it as is?
さっさーのままですか?
ah.
あー
I won't let it out, inside.
出しないよ、中に
Will we meet again?
また会ってくれる?